<resources>

    <string name="app_name">XYZ Readerx</string>
    <string name="welcome_xyz_reader">Welcome to XYZ Reader!</string>

    <string name="action_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>

    <string name="up">Up</string>

    <string name="card_sub_header">%1$s by %2$s</string>


    <string name="transition_photo">transition_photo</string>



    <string name="lorem">Beard sartorial brunch, kombucha roof party chartreuse biodiesel paleo chicharrones you probably haven\'t heard of them thundercats. Viral williamsburg forage sartorial, kombucha vegan four loko keytar food truck squid cliche. Yuccie selvage farm-to-table wayfarers shabby chic williamsburg sustainable, fashion axe cray. PBR&amp;B farm-to-table organic health goth meditation, four loko readymade. Neutra art party waistcoat gentrify, wayfarers stumptown selfies messenger bag shabby chic mixtape thundercats microdosing banjo roof party. Roof party tilde gastropub sartorial jean shorts literally. Blog tattooed pour-over tote bag, leggings jean shorts iPhone yuccie narwhal photo booth banh mi post-ironic.

Direct trade chia drinking vinegar sartorial pop-up, street art single-origin coffee before they sold out tofu messenger bag YOLO irony biodiesel squid. Normcore pitchfork paleo banjo, stumptown drinking vinegar kombucha master cleanse. Everyday carry godard slow-carb quinoa, cornhole readymade williamsburg vice. Leggings cred waistcoat, sustainable ugh 90\'s chicharrones. Williamsburg dreamcatcher viral, blue bottle +1 wolf master cleanse poutine pour-over austin tofu bushwick. Ugh heirloom locavore pabst, small batch fap kinfolk mixtape disrupt mlkshk polaroid banjo craft beer. Kombucha pickled mumblecore organic, freegan ennui microdosing deep v vice pop-up tumblr.

Fashion axe squid tote bag, you probably haven\'t heard of them stumptown chillwave meggings whatever sriracha skateboard DIY master cleanse before they sold out cray listicle. Tilde everyday carry +1 vinyl tacos readymade. Fanny pack pickled mixtape, ugh chambray post-ironic banjo vice asymmetrical sartorial pop-up. Roof party letterpress mustache, portland bicycle rights four dollar toast hoodie +1 kitsch tattooed locavore butcher neutra. Gastropub raw denim four loko, mixtape schlitz chia food truck squid pop-up XOXO tacos aesthetic cold-pressed chillwave roof party. Flannel put a bird on it gentrify tousled master cleanse direct trade. Beard biodiesel drinking vinegar truffaut, wolf plaid pork belly meggings deep v ramps.

Try-hard quinoa deep v cardigan freegan. Seitan bicycle rights poutine williamsburg artisan yr. Gluten-free master cleanse health goth, retro selvage twee chartreuse. Chartreuse pickled migas street art, vinyl meh chillwave trust fund cronut schlitz put a bird on it kitsch. Vice locavore 3 wolf moon gluten-free, occupy chicharrones photo booth actually. VHS disrupt cred polaroid, lo-fi master cleanse irony blue bottle portland ugh four dollar toast typewriter knausgaard cliche actually. Taxidermy tote bag chicharrones pop-up marfa, art party freegan poutine hashtag +1 ethical cronut chia VHS blue bottle.</string>


</resources>
